[{"type":"Multiple choice","question":"Er","A":"Beryllium","B":"Mercury","C":"Europium","D":"Chlorine","E":"Erbium","correct":"E"},{"type":"Multiple choice","question":"Mo","A":"Molybdenum","B":"Californium","C":"Bohrium","D":"Antimony","E":"Ununoctium","correct":"A"},{"type":"Multiple choice","question":"Ce","A":"Copernicium","B":"Cerium","C":"Copper","D":"Chlorine","E":"Cesium","correct":"B"},{"type":"Multiple choice","question":"Li","A":"Lithium","B":"Lawrencium","C":"Livermorium","D":"Lutetium","E":"Platinum","correct":"A"},{"type":"Multiple choice","question":"Y","A":"Ytterbium","B":"Praseodymium","C":"Beryllium","D":"Yttrium","E":"Dysprosium","correct":"D"},{"type":"Multiple choice","question":"Db","A":"Dysprosium","B":"Dubnium","C":"Molybdenum","D":"Rubidium","E":"Darmstadtium","correct":"B"},{"type":"Multiple choice","question":"Rh","A":"Rhodium","B":"Rhenium","C":"Rutherfordium","D":"Ruthenium","E":"Radium","correct":"A"},{"type":"Multiple choice","question":"Ga","A":"Germanium","B":"Gallium","C":"Gold","D":"Seaborgium","E":"Gadolinium","correct":"B"},{"type":"Multiple choice","question":"Pm","A":"Praseodymium","B":"Protactinium","C":"Potassium","D":"Plutonium","E":"Promethium","correct":"E"},{"type":"Multiple choice","question":"Ba","A":"Barium","B":"Boron","C":"Berkelium","D":"Carbon","E":"Bohrium","correct":"A"},{"type":"Multiple choice","question":"Pa","A":"Platinum","B":"Potassium","C":"Praseodymium","D":"Palladium","E":"Protactinium","correct":"E"},{"type":"Multiple choice","question":"K","A":"Darmstadtium","B":"Potassium","C":"Berkelium","D":"Nickel","E":"Krypton","correct":"B"},{"type":"Multiple choice","question":"B","A":"Berkelium","B":"Bohrium","C":"Bismuth","D":"Barium","E":"Boron","correct":"E"},{"type":"Multiple choice","question":"Dy","A":"Hydrogen","B":"Dysprosium","C":"Dubnium","D":"Neodymium","E":"Praseodymium","correct":"B"},{"type":"Multiple choice","question":"Ti","A":"Terbium","B":"Thorium","C":"Tellurium","D":"Thallium","E":"Titanium","correct":"E"},{"type":"Multiple choice","question":"F","A":"Fluorine","B":"Fermium","C":"Californium","D":"Francium","E":"Flerovium","correct":"A"},{"type":"Multiple choice","question":"Sm","A":"Samarium","B":"Selenium","C":"Strontium","D":"Sodium","E":"Scandium","correct":"A"},{"type":"Multiple choice","question":"Fr","A":"Francium","B":"Fermium","C":"Fluorine","D":"Californium","E":"Flerovium","correct":"A"},{"type":"Multiple choice","question":"Fl","A":"Flerovium","B":"Sulfur","C":"Fermium","D":"Californium","E":"Fluorine","correct":"A"},{"type":"Multiple choice","question":"Ir","A":"Iridium","B":"Iodine","C":"Germanium","D":"Bohrium","E":"Iron","correct":"A"},{"type":"Multiple choice","question":"Cs","A":"Cobalt","B":"Cesium","C":"Cadmium","D":"Arsenic","E":"Curium","correct":"B"},{"type":"Multiple choice","question":"Am","A":"Antimony","B":"Lanthanum","C":"Actinium","D":"Americium","E":"Aluminum","correct":"D"},{"type":"Multiple choice","question":"Pr","A":"Potassium","B":"Protactinium","C":"Promethium","D":"Praseodymium","E":"Phosphorus","correct":"D"},{"type":"Multiple choice","question":"Ds","A":"Scandium","B":"Darmstadtium","C":"Praseodymium","D":"Dubnium","E":"Dysprosium","correct":"B"},{"type":"Multiple choice","question":"Hf","A":"Hafnium","B":"Holmium","C":"Helium","D":"Rutherfordium","E":"Hassium","correct":"A"},{"type":"Multiple choice","question":"Th","A":"Terbium","B":"Thulium","C":"Technetium","D":"Thorium","E":"Thallium","correct":"D"},{"type":"Multiple choice","question":"Cf","A":"Cesium","B":"Curium","C":"Francium","D":"Cerium","E":"Californium","correct":"E"},{"type":"Multiple choice","question":"Ta","A":"Tungsten","B":"Antimony","C":"Titanium","D":"Thallium","E":"Tantalum","correct":"E"},{"type":"Multiple choice","question":"As","A":"Aluminum","B":"Potassium","C":"Arsenic","D":"Astatine","E":"Magnesium","correct":"C"},{"type":"Multiple choice","question":"P","A":"Plutonium","B":"Protactinium","C":"Palladium","D":"Polonium","E":"Phosphorus","correct":"E"},{"type":"Multiple choice","question":"Md","A":"Neodymium","B":"Molybdenum","C":"Rutherfordium","D":"Dysprosium","E":"Mendelevium","correct":"E"},{"type":"Multiple choice","question":"Pt","A":"Platinum","B":"Potassium","C":"Protactinium","D":"Plutonium","E":"Promethium","correct":"A"},{"type":"Multiple choice","question":"La","A":"Lead","B":"Lithium","C":"Aluminum","D":"Lawrencium","E":"Lanthanum","correct":"E"},{"type":"Multiple choice","question":"Hg","A":"Hassium","B":"Hydrogen","C":"Helium","D":"Mercury","E":"Holmium","correct":"D"},{"type":"Multiple choice","question":"Pd","A":"Palladium","B":"Praseodymium","C":"Phosphorus","D":"Promethium","E":"Platinum","correct":"A"},{"type":"Multiple choice","question":"Xe","A":"Oxygen","B":"Manganese","C":"Astatine","D":"Seaborgium","E":"Xenon","correct":"E"},{"type":"Multiple choice","question":"Tl","A":"Lutetium","B":"Tantalum","C":"Thulium","D":"Thallium","E":"Tellurium","correct":"D"},{"type":"Multiple choice","question":"Ra","A":"Lawrencium","B":"Radium","C":"Radon","D":"Protactinium","E":"Rubidium","correct":"B"},{"type":"Multiple choice","question":"At","A":"Astatine","B":"Argon","C":"Actinium","D":"Antimony","E":"Americium","correct":"A"},{"type":"Multiple choice","question":"Hs","A":"Holmium","B":"Hydrogen","C":"Hassium","D":"Hafnium","E":"Bismuth","correct":"C"},{"type":"Multiple choice","question":"Cl","A":"Chlorine","B":"Silicon","C":"Calcium","D":"Cobalt","E":"Californium","correct":"A"},{"type":"Multiple choice","question":"Uut","A":"Ununoctium","B":"Ununtrium","C":"Ununpentium","D":"Lutetium","E":"Ununseptium","correct":"B"},{"type":"Multiple choice","question":"S","A":"Strontium","B":"Seaborgium","C":"Silver","D":"Samarium","E":"Sulfur","correct":"E"},{"type":"Multiple choice","question":"O","A":"Copernicium","B":"Ununoctium","C":"Oxygen","D":"Osmium","E":"Boron","correct":"C"},{"type":"Multiple choice","question":"Sc","A":"Sulfur","B":"Scandium","C":"Seaborgium","D":"Silicon","E":"Sodium","correct":"B"},{"type":"Multiple choice","question":"Ho","A":"Hydrogen","B":"Chromium","C":"Hafnium","D":"Helium","E":"Holmium","correct":"E"},{"type":"Multiple choice","question":"Zr","A":"Zinc","B":"Zirconium","C":"Livermorium","D":"Tellurium","E":"Bromine","correct":"B"},{"type":"Multiple choice","question":"Re","A":"Roentgenium","B":"Fermium","C":"Rutherfordium","D":"Ruthenium","E":"Rhenium","correct":"E"},{"type":"Multiple choice","question":"No","A":"Nobelium","B":"Neodymium","C":"Neon","D":"Nitrogen","E":"Niobium","correct":"A"},{"type":"Multiple choice","question":"Bi","A":"Bismuth","B":"Berkelium","C":"Bohrium","D":"Beryllium","E":"Barium","correct":"A"},{"type":"Multiple choice","question":"N","A":"Neptunium","B":"Neon","C":"Nitrogen","D":"Neodymium","E":"Niobium","correct":"C"},{"type":"Multiple choice","question":"Nd","A":"Gadolinium","B":"Dubnium","C":"Neodymium","D":"Vanadium","E":"Neptunium","correct":"C"},{"type":"Multiple choice","question":"Gd","A":"Hydrogen","B":"Gallium","C":"Gadolinium","D":"Germanium","E":"Gold","correct":"C"},{"type":"Multiple choice","question":"Te","A":"Tellurium","B":"Tungsten","C":"Terbium","D":"Meitnerium","E":"Technetium","correct":"A"},{"type":"Multiple choice","question":"Rf","A":"Ruthenium","B":"Rhenium","C":"Fermium","D":"Roentgenium","E":"Rutherfordium","correct":"E"},{"type":"Multiple choice","question":"Eu","A":"Neodymium","B":"Lawrencium","C":"Europium","D":"Erbium","E":"Einsteinium","correct":"C"},{"type":"Multiple choice","question":"Cr","A":"Copernicium","B":"Californium","C":"Chromium","D":"Cerium","E":"Chlorine","correct":"C"},{"type":"Multiple choice","question":"Br","A":"Berkelium","B":"Bohrium","C":"Boron","D":"Bromine","E":"Barium","correct":"D"},{"type":"Multiple choice","question":"Cm","A":"Chromium","B":"Californium","C":"Cadmium","D":"Curium","E":"Copernicium","correct":"D"},{"type":"Multiple choice","question":"Ru","A":"Rhodium","B":"Roentgenium","C":"Rhenium","D":"Radium","E":"Ruthenium","correct":"E"},{"type":"Multiple choice","question":"Np","A":"Nobelium","B":"Neptunium","C":"Polonium","D":"Ununpentium","E":"Ununseptium","correct":"B"},{"type":"Multiple choice","question":"He","A":"Hydrogen","B":"Chlorine","C":"Rhenium","D":"Rutherfordium","E":"Helium","correct":"E"},{"type":"Multiple choice","question":"Pb","A":"Phosphorus","B":"Platinum","C":"Palladium","D":"Lead","E":"Plutonium","correct":"D"},{"type":"Multiple choice","question":"Ar","A":"Americium","B":"Darmstadtium","C":"Seaborgium","D":"Argon","E":"Arsenic","correct":"D"},{"type":"Multiple choice","question":"Sb","A":"Antimony","B":"Strontium","C":"Sulfur","D":"Seaborgium","E":"Sodium","correct":"A"},{"type":"Multiple choice","question":"Lr","A":"Tellurium","B":"Lithium","C":"Livermorium","D":"Lawrencium","E":"Flerovium","correct":"D"},{"type":"Multiple choice","question":"Ag","A":"Argon","B":"Silver","C":"Astatine","D":"Seaborgium","E":"Germanium","correct":"B"},{"type":"Multiple choice","question":"W","A":"Molybdenum","B":"Lawrencium","C":"Oxygen","D":"Radium","E":"Tungsten","correct":"E"},{"type":"Multiple choice","question":"Mt","A":"Rutherfordium","B":"Plutonium","C":"Potassium","D":"Strontium","E":"Meitnerium","correct":"E"},{"type":"Multiple choice","question":"Cn","A":"Californium","B":"Copernicium","C":"Carbon","D":"Ununoctium","E":"Chlorine","correct":"B"},{"type":"Multiple choice","question":"Uup","A":"Ununoctium","B":"Promethium","C":"Phosphorus","D":"Ununseptium","E":"Ununpentium","correct":"E"},{"type":"Multiple choice","question":"Ac","A":"Antimony","B":"Americium","C":"Actinium","D":"Aluminum","E":"Arsenic","correct":"C"},{"type":"Multiple choice","question":"Fe","A":"Flerovium","B":"Iron","C":"Rutherfordium","D":"Fluorine","E":"Fermium","correct":"B"},{"type":"Multiple choice","question":"Es","A":"Seaborgium","B":"Silver","C":"Cesium","D":"Praseodymium","E":"Einsteinium","correct":"E"},{"type":"Multiple choice","question":"C","A":"Chlorine","B":"Copper","C":"Carbon","D":"Cadmium","E":"Cesium","correct":"C"},{"type":"Multiple choice","question":"Se","A":"Silver","B":"Arsenic","C":"Selenium","D":"Silicon","E":"Seaborgium","correct":"C"},{"type":"Multiple choice","question":"Zn","A":"Oxygen","B":"Zinc","C":"Niobium","D":"Iodine","E":"Zirconium","correct":"B"},{"type":"Multiple choice","question":"Sn","A":"Tin","B":"Selenium","C":"Scandium","D":"Strontium","E":"Silicon","correct":"A"},{"type":"Multiple choice","question":"U","A":"Ununoctium","B":"Ununpentium","C":"Uranium","D":"Ununtrium","E":"Ununseptium","correct":"C"},{"type":"Multiple choice","question":"Cd","A":"Californium","B":"Cadmium","C":"Scandium","D":"Cobalt","E":"Copernicium","correct":"B"},{"type":"Multiple choice","question":"Nb","A":"Niobium","B":"Neon","C":"Nickel","D":"Nobelium","E":"Nitrogen","correct":"A"},{"type":"Multiple choice","question":"Ne","A":"Nobelium","B":"Neptunium","C":"Neon","D":"Nitrogen","E":"Nickel","correct":"C"},{"type":"Multiple choice","question":"Mg","A":"Seaborgium","B":"Mercury","C":"Mendelevium","D":"Manganese","E":"Magnesium","correct":"E"},{"type":"Multiple choice","question":"Au","A":"Gold","B":"Americium","C":"Actinium","D":"Aluminum","E":"Gadolinium","correct":"A"},{"type":"Multiple choice","question":"Os","A":"Strontium","B":"Praseodymium","C":"Sodium","D":"Osmium","E":"Oxygen","correct":"D"},{"type":"Multiple choice","question":"I","A":"Iodine","B":"Indium","C":"Iridium","D":"Iron","E":"Germanium","correct":"A"},{"type":"Multiple choice","question":"Uuo","A":"Protactinium","B":"Nobelium","C":"Holmium","D":"Ununoctium","E":"Ununseptium","correct":"D"},{"type":"Multiple choice","question":"H","A":"Helium","B":"Holmium","C":"Hafnium","D":"Hydrogen","E":"Hassium","correct":"D"},{"type":"Multiple choice","question":"Fm","A":"Californium","B":"Fluorine","C":"Flerovium","D":"Fermium","E":"Francium","correct":"D"},{"type":"Multiple choice","question":"Mn","A":"Mendelevium","B":"Manganese","C":"Magnesium","D":"Meitnerium","E":"Molybdenum","correct":"B"},{"type":"Multiple choice","question":"Na","A":"Sodium","B":"Actinium","C":"Carbon","D":"Protactinium","E":"Vanadium","correct":"A"},{"type":"Multiple choice","question":"Be","A":"Beryllium","B":"Terbium","C":"Bromine","D":"Barium","E":"Berkelium","correct":"A"},{"type":"Multiple choice","question":"Tb","A":"Thallium","B":"Terbium","C":"Cobalt","D":"Tungsten","E":"Titanium","correct":"B"},{"type":"Multiple choice","question":"Si","A":"Silicon","B":"Scandium","C":"Selenium","D":"Sodium","E":"Samarium","correct":"A"},{"type":"Multiple choice","question":"Bh","A":"Berkelium","B":"Bromine","C":"Bismuth","D":"Beryllium","E":"Bohrium","correct":"E"},{"type":"Multiple choice","question":"Rb","A":"Rhenium","B":"Seaborgium","C":"Rubidium","D":"Berkelium","E":"Bohrium","correct":"C"},{"type":"Multiple choice","question":"Bk","A":"Beryllium","B":"Bromine","C":"Berkelium","D":"Bismuth","E":"Bohrium","correct":"C"},{"type":"Multiple choice","question":"Al","A":"Lead","B":"Actinium","C":"Gallium","D":"Aluminum","E":"Thallium","correct":"D"},{"type":"Multiple choice","question":"Rg","A":"Roentgenium","B":"Germanium","C":"Argon","D":"Rubidium","E":"Radon","correct":"A"},{"type":"Multiple choice","question":"Pu","A":"Palladium","B":"Plutonium","C":"Polonium","D":"Phosphorus","E":"Platinum","correct":"B"},{"type":"Multiple choice","question":"V","A":"Flerovium","B":"Silver","C":"Mendelevium","D":"Livermorium","E":"Vanadium","correct":"E"},{"type":"Multiple choice","question":"Po","A":"Promethium","B":"Phosphorus","C":"Protactinium","D":"Plutonium","E":"Polonium","correct":"E"},{"type":"Multiple choice","question":"Cu","A":"Copernicium","B":"Cesium","C":"Cerium","D":"Chromium","E":"Copper","correct":"E"},{"type":"Multiple choice","question":"Ca","A":"Cadmium","B":"Cobalt","C":"Californium","D":"Carbon","E":"Calcium","correct":"E"},{"type":"Multiple choice","question":"Lv","A":"Lutetium","B":"Livermorium","C":"Lead","D":"Lanthanum","E":"Silver","correct":"B"},{"type":"Multiple choice","question":"Kr","A":"Radon","B":"Krypton","C":"Strontium","D":"Chromium","E":"Berkelium","correct":"B"},{"type":"Multiple choice","question":"Tc","A":"Technetium","B":"Titanium","C":"Thallium","D":"Terbium","E":"Tungsten","correct":"A"},{"type":"Multiple choice","question":"In","A":"Ununseptium","B":"Iron","C":"Indium","D":"Iodine","E":"Ununpentium","correct":"C"},{"type":"Multiple choice","question":"Sr","A":"Seaborgium","B":"Strontium","C":"Silver","D":"Sulfur","E":"Samarium","correct":"B"},{"type":"Multiple choice","question":"Tm","A":"Thulium","B":"Tellurium","C":"Terbium","D":"Tantalum","E":"Technetium","correct":"A"},{"type":"Multiple choice","question":"Uus","A":"Praseodymium","B":"Ununtrium","C":"Seaborgium","D":"Sodium","E":"Ununseptium","correct":"E"},{"type":"Multiple choice","question":"Ni","A":"Neodymium","B":"Nickel","C":"Nitrogen","D":"Neptunium","E":"Niobium","correct":"B"},{"type":"Multiple choice","question":"Sg","A":"Scandium","B":"Samarium","C":"Magnesium","D":"Seaborgium","E":"Sodium","correct":"D"},{"type":"Multiple choice","question":"Co","A":"Chromium","B":"Cobalt","C":"Copper","D":"Carbon","E":"Chlorine","correct":"B"},{"type":"Multiple choice","question":"Lu","A":"Lanthanum","B":"Lutetium","C":"Livermorium","D":"Lawrencium","E":"Lithium","correct":"B"},{"type":"Multiple choice","question":"Rn","A":"Roentgenium","B":"Radon","C":"Rhenium","D":"Uranium","E":"Ruthenium","correct":"B"},{"type":"Multiple choice","question":"Ge","A":"Gold","B":"Gallium","C":"Tungsten","D":"Germanium","E":"Hydrogen","correct":"D"},{"type":"Multiple choice","question":"Yb","A":"Rubidium","B":"Molybdenum","C":"Beryllium","D":"Ytterbium","E":"Yttrium","correct":"D"}]